Adrià Mitjavila Ventura

Bioinformatician

☆ Girona (Spain) - Milan (Italy)

☐ adria.mitjavila94@gmail.com amitjavilaventura.github.io amitjavilaventura amitjavilaventura

Biotechnologist living around computers, pursuing a PhD in Computational Biology and interested in data analysis to support experimental research as well as in pure computational experiments and in software/pipeline development.

Education _

Scuola Europea di Medicina Molecolare, PhD. Computational Biology

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, MSc. Bioinformatics and Biostatistics

2018 - Present
Universidad de Sevilla, MSc. Molecular Genetics and Biotechnology

2017 - 2018
Universitat de Girona, BSC. Biotechnology

Employment _____

Milan (Italy)
10/2019 - Present
07/2019 - 10/2019
Seville (Spain)
07/2018 - 10/2018
09/2017 - 07/2018
Girona (Spain)
07/2017 - 09/2017
Girona (Spain)
01/2017 - 06/2017
09/2016 - 06/2017

Publications

JOURNAL ARTICLES

Begley et al. 2020 Xrn1 influence on gene transcription results from the combination of general effects on elongating RNA pol II and gene-specific chromatin configuration. RNA Biology. DOI: 10.1080/15476286.2020.1845504.

References _

Available upon request.

Updated: Jan. 24, 2021 1/1